(function(e){function t(t){for(var o,i,s=t[0],c=t[1],m=t[2],l=0,g=[];l<s.length;l++)i=s[l],Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(r,i)&&r[i]&&g.push(r[i][0]),r[i]=0;for(o in c)Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(c,o)&&(e[o]=c[o]);u&&u(t);while(g.length)g.shift()();return n.push.apply(n,m||[]),a()}function a(){for(var e,t=0;t<n.length;t++){for(var a=n[t],o=!0,i=1;i<a.length;i++){var c=a[i];0!==r[c]&&(o=!1)}o&&(n.splice(t--,1),e=s(s.s=a[0]))}return e}var o={},r={app:0},n=[];function i(e){return s.p+"js/"+({}[e]||e)+"."+{"chunk-1335a3e6":"92736b06"}[e]+".js"}function s(t){if(o[t])return o[t].exports;var a=o[t]={i:t,l:!1,exports:{}};return e[t].call(a.exports,a,a.exports,s),a.l=!0,a.exports}s.e=function(e){var t=[],a=r[e];if(0!==a)if(a)t.push(a[2]);else{var o=new Promise((function(t,o){a=r[e]=[t,o]}));t.push(a[2]=o);var n,c=document.createElement("script");c.charset="utf-8",c.timeout=120,s.nc&&c.setAttribute("nonce",s.nc),c.src=i(e);var m=new Error;n=function(t){c.onerror=c.onload=null,clearTimeout(l);var a=r[e];if(0!==a){if(a){var o=t&&("load"===t.type?"missing":t.type),n=t&&t.target&&t.target.src;m.message="Loading chunk "+e+" failed.\n("+o+": "+n+")",m.name="ChunkLoadError",m.type=o,m.request=n,a[1](m)}r[e]=void 0}};var l=setTimeout((function(){n({type:"timeout",target:c})}),12e4);c.onerror=c.onload=n,document.head.appendChild(c)}return Promise.all(t)},s.m=e,s.c=o,s.d=function(e,t,a){s.o(e,t)||Object.defineProperty(e,t,{enumerable:!0,get:a})},s.r=function(e){"undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.toStringTag&&Object.defineProperty(e,Symbol.toStringTag,{value:"Module"}),Object.defineProperty(e,"__esModule",{value:!0})},s.t=function(e,t){if(1&t&&(e=s(e)),8&t)return e;if(4&t&&"object"===typeof e&&e&&e.__esModule)return e;var a=Object.create(null);if(s.r(a),Object.defineProperty(a,"default",{enumerable:!0,value:e}),2&t&&"string"!=typeof e)for(var o in e)s.d(a,o,function(t){return e[t]}.bind(null,o));return a},s.n=function(e){var t=e&&e.__esModule?function(){return e["default"]}:function(){return e};return s.d(t,"a",t),t},s.o=function(e,t){return Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)},s.p="/magpie3-qa-overinfo-free-production/",s.oe=function(e){throw console.error(e),e};var c=window["webpackJsonp"]=window["webpackJsonp"]||[],m=c.push.bind(c);c.push=t,c=c.slice();for(var l=0;l<c.length;l++)t(c[l]);var u=m;n.push([0,"chunk-vendors"]),a()})({0:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a("56d7")},1:function(e,t){},2:function(e,t){},"254e":function(e,t){e.exports=[{itemName:"cafe-pie",settingName:"cafe",vignette_start:"You are a server in a café. Today the café has",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks: ",question:"Do you have raspberry cake?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have raspberry cake today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"raspberry cake",competitor:"raspberry pie",sameCategory1:"lemon cake",sameCategory2:"chocolate cookies",otherCategory1:"pasta al forno",otherCategory2:"cheese pizza",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"cafe-pizza",settingName:"cafe",vignette_start:"You are a server in a café. Today the café has ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks: ",question:"Do you have veggie pizza?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have veggie pizza today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"veggie pizza",competitor:"cheese pizza",sameCategory1:"pepperoni pizza",sameCategory2:"lasagna",otherCategory1:"raspberry pie",otherCategory2:"chocolate cookies",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"bar-whiteWine",settingName:"bar",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nLate at night a woman walks in. She looks gloomy. She says:",question:"Do you have Sauvignon Blanc?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have Sauvignon Blanc today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"sauvignon blanc",competitor:"Chardonnay",sameCategory1:"whiskey",sameCategory2:"craft beer",otherCategory1:"homemade lemonade",otherCategory2:"coffee",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"bar-tea",settingName:"bar",vignette_start:"You are a bartender in a hotel bar. The bar serves only",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in. She says:",question:"Do you have sweet tea?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have sweet tea today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"sweet tea",competitor:"homemade lemonade",sameCategory1:"iced coffee",sameCategory2:"soda",otherCategory1:"craft beer",otherCategory2:"Chardonnay",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"movie-fantasy",settingName:"movie",vignette_start:"You work at the ticket counter of a small movie theatre. You are currently playing ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks:",question:"Are you playing a fantasy movie today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we aren’t playing a fantasy movie today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a fantasy movie",competitor:"an animated film",sameCategory1:"a comedy",sameCategory2:"a musical",otherCategory1:"a horror movie",otherCategory2:"an adventure movie",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"movie-western",settingName:"movie",vignette_start:"You work at the ticket counter of a small movie theatre. You are currently playing ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer asks:",question:"Are you playing a Western movie today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we aren’t playing a Western movie today.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a Western movie",competitor:"an adventure movie",sameCategory1:"a science fiction movie",sameCategory2:"a film noir",otherCategory1:"a cartoon",otherCategory2:"an animated film",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"touristInfo-childTheatre",settingName:"touristInfo",vignette_start:"You are working in a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening: ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks:",question:"Is there a theatre performance for children today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no theatre performance for children today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a theatre performance for children",competitor:"a circus show",sameCategory1:"a flea market",sameCategory2:"a trade fare",otherCategory1:"a rock concert",otherCategory2:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"touristInfo-clubbing",settingName:"touristInfo",vignette_start:"You are working in a tourist office in a medium-sized tourist town. Today the following events are happening: ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young woman walks in and asks:",question:"Is there a club event with electronic music today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no club event with electronic music today.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a club event with electronic music",competitor:"a club event with a hip hop DJ",sameCategory1:"a rock concert",sameCategory2:"live jazz music",otherCategory1:"a circus show",otherCategory2:"a street dance performance",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"bookingAgency-lowClassAccommodation",settingName:"bookingAgency",vignette_start:"You work in a travel booking agency in a medium-sized tourist town. The following types of accommodation are still available for tomorrow night:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks:",question:"Is there a bed in the youth hostel available for tomorrow night?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there are no more beds available in the youth hostel available for tomorrow night.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a bed in the youth hostel",competitor:"a couch surfing place",sameCategory1:"a room in a budget hotel",sameCategory2:"a room in a cheap bed-and-breakfast",otherCategory1:"a suite in a four-star hotel",otherCategory2:"an expensive lodge close to the city",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"bookingAgency-highClassAccommodation",settingName:"bookingAgency",vignette_start:"You work in a travel booking agency in a medium-sized tourist town. The following types of accommodation are still available for tomorrow night: ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAn older man walks in and asks: ",question:"Is a single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no single room in a five-star hotel available for tomorrow night.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a single room in a five-star hotel",competitor:"a suite in a four-star hotel",sameCategory1:"a penthouse apartment",sameCategory2:"an expensive lodge close to the city",otherCategory1:"a place for couch surfing",otherCategory2:"a room in a cheap bed-and-breakfast",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"waterSport-motor",settingName:"waterSport",vignette_start:"You work in a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks:",question:"Do you rent jet skis?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent jet skis.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"jet skis",competitor:"water ski equipment",sameCategory1:"small sailboats",sameCategory2:"speedboats",otherCategory1:"pedal boats",otherCategory2:"kayaks",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"waterSport-muscle",settingName:"waterSport",vignette_start:"You work in a water sports rental agency in a popular tourist region with a large lake for different types of water sports. The agency offers ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer calls on the phone and asks:",question:"Do you rent canoes?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t rent canoes.",answer_template:"We rent *.",itemQuestion:"canoes",competitor:"kayaks",sameCategory1:"pedal boats",sameCategory2:"rowing boats",otherCategory1:"speedboats",otherCategory2:"water ski equipment",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"dutyFree-smokes",settingName:"dutyFree",vignette_start:"You are a flight attendant on an old-fashioned international flight. You are selling duty-free items to passengers. You currently have the following items on offer:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs you walk by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cigars?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cigars.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cigars",competitor:"cigarettes",sameCategory1:"gin",sameCategory2:"whiskey",otherCategory1:"Swiss chocolate",otherCategory2:"gingerbread",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"dutyFree-sweets",settingName:"dutyFree",vignette_start:"You are a flight attendant on an old-fashioned international flight. You are selling duty free items to passengers. You currently have the following items on offer: ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nAs you walk by, a passenger asks:",question:"Do you sell cookies?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t sell cookies.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"cookies",competitor:"gingerbread",sameCategory1:"waffles",sameCategory2:"Swiss chocolate",otherCategory1:"cigarettes",otherCategory2:"whiskey",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"clothing-beach",settingName:"clothing",vignette_start:"You work at a small designer clothing store. You currently have the following items in stock: ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer comes in and asks:",question:"Do you have any Hawaiian shirts?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any Hawaiian shirts.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Hawaiian shirts",competitor:"t-shirts",sameCategory1:"shorts",sameCategory2:"tank tops",otherCategory1:"sweatshirts",otherCategory2:"hoodies",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"clothing-winter",settingName:"clothing",vignette_start:"You work at a small designer clothing store. You currently have the following items in stock: ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA customer comes in and asks:",question:"Do you have any wool sweaters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any wool sweaters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"wool sweaters",competitor:"sweatshirts",sameCategory1:"hoodies",sameCategory2:"winter coats",otherCategory1:"t-shirts",otherCategory2:"shorts",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"petAdoption-dogs",settingName:"petAdoption",vignette_start:"You work at an adoption center for rescued animals. You currently have the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks:",question:"Do you have any Dalmatians?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any Dalmatians.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"Dalmatians",competitor:"chocolate labs",sameCategory1:"golden retrievers",sameCategory2:"terriers",otherCategory1:"Siamese cats",otherCategory2:"gerbils",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"petAdoption-hamster",settingName:"petAdoption",vignette_start:"You work at an adoption center for rescued animals. You currently have the following animals at the center:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family comes in and asks:",question:"Do you have any hamsters?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have any hamsters.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"hamsters",competitor:"gerbils",sameCategory1:"mice",sameCategory2:"ferrets",otherCategory1:"chocolate labs",otherCategory2:"Great Danes",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"furniture-indoors",settingName:"furniture",vignette_start:"You work at a vintage furniture store. You currently have on display ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family walks in and asks:",question:"Do you have an armchair?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have an armchair in stock.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"an armchair",competitor:"a sofa",sameCategory1:"a bean bag chair",sameCategory2:"a rocking chair",otherCategory1:"a wooden bench",otherCategory2:"a porch swing",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"furniture-outdoors",settingName:"furniture",vignette_start:"You work at a vintage furniture store. You currently have on display ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA family walks in and asks:",question:"Do you have a deck chair?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a deck chair in stock.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a deck chair",competitor:"a porch swing",sameCategory1:"a wicker-back cane chair",sameCategory2:"a wooden bench",otherCategory1:"a sofa",otherCategory2:"a leather recliner",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"books-romance",settingName:"books",vignette_start:"You work at a bookshop in a small town. You currently have",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks:",question:"Do you have a book of love poems?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have love poems.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"love poems",competitor:"books of French love letters",sameCategory1:"romance novels",sameCategory2:"historical dramas",otherCategory1:"thrillers",otherCategory2:"science fiction novels",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"books-fantasy",settingName:"books",vignette_start:"You work at a bookshop in a small town. You currently have",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA student walks in and asks:",question:"Do you sell fantasy novels?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t sell fantasy novels.",answer_template:"We sell *.",itemQuestion:"fantasy novels",competitor:"science fiction novels",sameCategory1:"adventure novels",sameCategory2:"mysteries",otherCategory1:"books of French love letters",otherCategory2:"romance novels",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"electronics-laptop",settingName:"electronics",vignette_start:"You work at a second hand electronics store. You currently have",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks:",question:"Do you have a MacBook Pro?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a MacBook Pro.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a MacBook Pro",competitor:"a MacBook Air",sameCategory1:"a desktop computer",sameCategory2:"a Dell laptop",otherCategory1:"a TV",otherCategory2:"an Xbox",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"electronics-console",settingName:"electronics",vignette_start:"You work at a second hand electronics store. There are currently",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks:",question:"Do you have a PlayStation?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have a PlayStation.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"a PlayStation",competitor:"an Xbox",sameCategory1:"a Wii",sameCategory2:"a Nintendo Switch",otherCategory1:"a desktop computer",otherCategory2:"a MacBook Air",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"gym-yoga",settingName:"gymActivities",vignette_start:"You work at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA woman walks in and asks:",question:"Do you offer yoga classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have yoga.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"yoga classes",competitor:"a pilates class",sameCategory1:"an aerobics class",sameCategory2:"zumba classes",otherCategory1:"kickboxing",otherCategory2:"karate classes",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"gym-boxing",settingName:"gymActivities",vignette_start:"You work at the reception desk of a gym. The gym currently offers",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young guy walks in and asks:",question:"Do you offer boxing classes?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, we don’t have boxing.",answer_template:"We have *.",itemQuestion:"boxing classes",competitor:"kickboxing classes",sameCategory1:"judo",sameCategory2:"karate classes",otherCategory1:"aerobics",otherCategory2:"pilates",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"kidsActivities-crafts",settingName:"kidsActivities",vignette_start:"You are a teacher at a summer camp. Today a new group of children arrived. They need to sign up for different activities. The camp offers ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA kid walks up to you and asks:",question:"Is there a pottery class?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no pottery class.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a pottery class",competitor:"a watercolor painting class",sameCategory1:"a sewing class",sameCategory2:"an origami class",otherCategory1:"a swimming class",otherCategory2:"an acrobatics class",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"kidsActivities-sports",settingName:"kidsActivities",vignette_start:"You are a teacher at a summer camp. Today a new group of children arrived. They need to sign up for different activities. The camp offers ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA kid walks up to you and asks:",question:"Is there a cheerleading class?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no cheerleading class.",answer_template:"There is *.",itemQuestion:"a cheerleading class",competitor:"an acrobatics class",sameCategory1:"a karate class",sameCategory2:"a dancing class",otherCategory1:"a watercolor painting class",otherCategory2:"a pottery class",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"friendsActivities-boardGames",settingName:"friendsActivities",vignette_start:"You are hosting a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at your house. For activities, you prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour friends arrive and ask you:",question:"Do you have the game Clue?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have the game Clue.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"the game Clue",competitor:"Monopoly",sameCategory1:"Twister",sameCategory2:"a poker set",otherCategory1:"PlayStation games",otherCategory2:"some movies",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"friendsActivities-videoEntertainment",settingName:"friendsActivities",vignette_start:"You are hosting a casual Saturday night get together with your friends at your house. For activities, you prepared",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour friends arrive and ask you:",question:"Do you have Xbox games?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have Xbox games.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"Xbox games",competitor:"PlayStation games",sameCategory1:"Wii games",sameCategory2:"some movies",otherCategory1:"a poker set",otherCategory2:"Monopoly",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"disney-action",settingName:"disney",vignette_start:"You work at the entrance gate for a theme park. Today visitors can see",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA group of kids walks in and asks:",question:"Can we see Superman?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, Superman is not here today.",answer_template:"* is here.",itemQuestion:"Superman",competitor:"Spiderman",sameCategory1:"Hulk",sameCategory2:"Batman",otherCategory1:"Ariel",otherCategory2:"Princess Elsa",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"disney-princess",settingName:"disney",vignette_start:"You work at the entrance gate for a theme park. Today visitors can see",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA group of kids walks in and asks:",question:"Can we see Moana?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, Moana is not here today.",answer_template:"* is here.",itemQuestion:"Moana",competitor:"Princess Elsa",sameCategory1:"Ariel",sameCategory2:"Cinderella",otherCategory1:"Spiderman",otherCategory2:"Batman",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"plants-green",settingName:"plants",vignette_start:"You like to grow beautiful plants and flowers in your house and garden. You often give away plants and bouquets to friends and family. You currently have ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits you and asks:",question:"Do you have an aloe vera plant?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have an aloe vera.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"an aloe vera",competitor:"an agave plant",sameCategory1:"an ivy vine",sameCategory2:"some bamboo",otherCategory1:"a rose bush",otherCategory2:"an orchid",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"plants-flowers",settingName:"plants",vignette_start:"You like to grow beautiful plants and flowers in your house and garden. You often give away plants and bouquets to friends and family. You currently have ",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA friend just moved and wants to get something to decorate her new apartment. She visits you and asks:",question:"Do you have peonies?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don’t have peonies.",answer_template:"I have *.",itemQuestion:"peonies",competitor:"tulips",sameCategory1:"sunflowers",sameCategory2:"a rose bush",otherCategory1:"an ivy vine",otherCategory2:"an agave plant",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"zoo-xl",settingName:"zoo",vignette_start:"You took your kids to the zoo today. You carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour eight-year-old is impatient and asks:",question:"Can we see the tiger?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, they don’t have a tiger here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a tiger",competitor:"a lion",sameCategory1:"gorillas",sameCategory2:"a giraffe",otherCategory1:"snakes",otherCategory2:"iguanas",correct_response:"main"},{itemName:"zoo-reptiles",settingName:"zoo",vignette_start:"You took your kids to the zoo today. You carefully studied the map of the zoo and saw that there is",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour eight-year-old is impatient and asks:",question:"Can we see the chameleon?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, they don't have chameleons here.",answer_template:"They have *.",itemQuestion:"a chameleon",competitor:"iguanas",sameCategory1:"turtles",sameCategory2:"snakes",otherCategory1:"a lion",otherCategory2:"gorillas",correct_response:"main"}]},"56d7":function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var o=a("2b0e"),r=a("7591"),n=a.n(r),i=a("3665"),s=function(){var e=this,t=e._self._c;return t("Experiment",{attrs:{title:"question-answering-experiment"}},[t("InstructionScreen",{attrs:{title:"Welcome"}},[e._v(" Thanks for taking part in our experiment! "),t("br"),t("br"),e._v(" In the following, you will see short descriptions of scenes in which a character asks a question. Your task is to write down an answer to that question. "),t("br"),t("br"),e._v(" Notice that there will also be simple attention checking trials. You will recognize them immediately when you read the important text on each trial carefully -- those trials contain instructions for you to type a certain word in the textbox. Please spell the words exactly as stated in the instructions. "),t("br"),t("br"),e._v(" Please answer like you would naturally do when you were in a situation like the one described on each screen. "),t("br"),e._v(" Please respond naturally and reasonably. "),t("br"),e._v(" Please avoid jokes, insults or otherwise making the dialogues into something else than simple, harmless exchanges of information. ")]),e._l(e.trials,(function(a,o){return[a.type?[t("FreetypingScreen",{key:o,attrs:{trial:a,trial_type:"filler",index:o,progress:o/e.trials.length}})]:[t("FreetypingScreen",{key:o,attrs:{trial:a,trial_type:"main",index:o,progress:o/e.trials.length}})]]})),t("PostTestScreen"),t("SubmitResultsScreen")],2)},c=[],m=a("2ef0"),l=a.n(m),u=a("254e"),g=a.n(u),h=a("d43f"),y=a.n(h),p=function(){var e=this,t=e._self._c;return t("Screen",{attrs:{progress:e.progress}},[t("Slide",[t("Record",{attrs:{data:{trialNr:e.index+1,itemName:e.trial.itemName,settingName:e.trial.settingName,trial_type:e.trial_type,correct_response:e.trial.correct_response}}}),e._l(e.createScreen.split("\\n"),(function(a,o){return t("span",{key:o},[e._v(" "+e._s(a)),t("br")])})),t("textarea",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.$magpie.measurements.answer,expression:"$magpie.measurements.answer"}],staticStyle:{width:"500px",height:"200px"},domProps:{value:e.$magpie.measurements.answer},on:{input:function(t){t.target.composing||e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"answer",t.target.value)}}}),e.$magpie.measurements.answer&&e.$magpie.measurements.answer.length>2?t("button",{on:{click:function(t){return e.$magpie.saveAndNextScreen()}}},[e._v(" Submit ")]):e._e()],2)],1)},d=[];function v(e){var t=l.a.shuffle(["competitor","sameCategory1","sameCategory2","otherCategory1","otherCategory2"]);console.log(t);var a=e.vignette_start,o=e.vignette_continuation,r=e.question;console.log(e.correct_response);var n=t.map(t=>e[t]);n.splice(-1,1,"and ".concat(n.at(-1)));n=n.join(", ").concat(".");var i=[a,n,o,'"'.concat(r).concat('"'),"\\n\\n","You reply: "].join(" ");return i}var f={name:"SliderRatingScreen",props:{trial:{type:Object,required:!0},trial_type:{type:String,required:!0},index:{type:Number,required:!0},progress:{type:Number,default:void 0}},methods:{createText:v},computed:{createScreen(){return v(this.trial)}}},w=f,k=a("2877"),_=Object(k["a"])(w,p,d,!1,null,null,null),C=_.exports,b=l.a.sample(["odd","even"]);const N=8,Y=3,A="odd"==b?g.a.filter((e,t)=>t%2===0):g.a.filter((e,t)=>t%2!=0),I="odd"==b?y.a.filter((e,t)=>t%2===0):y.a.filter((e,t)=>t%2!=0);document.onselectstart=()=>!1,document.oncontextmenu=()=>!1;var q={name:"App",components:{FreetypingScreen:C},data(){return{trials:l.a.shuffle(l.a.concat(l.a.sampleSize(A,N),l.a.sampleSize(I,Y)))}},computed:{_(){return l.a}}},x=q,T=(a("ddc9"),Object(k["a"])(x,s,c,!1,null,null,null)),S=T.exports,j={experimentId:"95",serverUrl:"https://mcmpact.ikw.uni-osnabrueck.de/magpie/",socketUrl:"wss://mcmpact.ikw.uni-osnabrueck.de/magpie/socket",completionUrl:"https://app.prolific.co/submissions/complete?cc=C1J3ETN9",contactEmail:"polina.tsvilodub@gmail.com",mode:"directLink",language:"en"};o["default"].config.productionTip=!1,o["default"].use(n.a,{prefix:"Canvas"}),o["default"].use(i["a"],j),new o["default"]({render:e=>e(S)}).$mount("#app")},d43f:function(e,t){e.exports=[{itemName:"jobCenter-office",settingName:"jobCenter",vignette_start:"You are working at the job center consultation desk and help people find open vacancies. Please type ‘teacher’ in the text area. Currently the following positions are available at local businesses:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA man walks in and asks:",question:"Is there an open accountant job?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no accountant job open.",answer_template:"There is *.",type:"filler",target:"an accountant job",competitor:"a bookkeeper job",sameCategory1:"a front desk secretary job",sameCategory2:"a manager assistant job",otherCategory1:"a carpenter job",otherCategory2:"a car mechanic job",correct_response:"teacher"},{itemName:"jobCenter-engineer",settingName:"jobCenter",vignette_start:"You are working at the job center consultation desk and help people find open vacancies. Please type ‘teacher’ in the text area. Currently the following positions are available at local businesses:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA man walks in and asks:",question:"Is there an electrical mechanic job open?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no electrical mechanic job open.",answer_template:"There is *.",type:"filler",target:"an electrical mechanic job",competitor:"an electrician job",sameCategory1:"a car mechanic job",sameCategory2:"an electrical engineer job",otherCategory1:"a secretary job",otherCategory2:"a bookkeeper job",correct_response:"teacher"},{itemName:"art-painting",settingName:"art",vignette_start:"You work at an art shop. You are hosting an exhibition sale by a local artist. The artist has",vignette_continuation:"Please type ‘sculpture’ in the text area. \\n\\nA customer takes a look around and asks:",question:"Are there any acrylic paintings for sale?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, there are no acrylic paintings.",answer_template:"There are *.",type:"filler",target:"acrylic paintings",competitor:"gouache paintings",sameCategory1:"watercolor paintings",sameCategory2:"oil paintings",otherCategory1:"pencil drawings",otherCategory2:"charcoal drawings",correct_response:"sculpture"},{itemName:"art-drawing",settingName:"art",vignette_start:"You work at an art shop. You are hosting an exhibition sale by a local artist. The artist has",vignette_continuation:"Please type ‘sculpture’ in the text area. \\n\\nA customer takes a look around and asks:",question:"Are there any ink drawings for sale?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, there are no ink drawings.",answer_template:"There are *.",type:"filler",target:"ink drawings",competitor:"pencil drawings",sameCategory1:"charcoal drawings",sameCategory2:"crayon drawings",otherCategory1:"gouache paintings",otherCategory2:"oil paintings",correct_response:"sculpture"},{itemName:"carRental-fun",settingName:"carRental",vignette_start:"You are working in a private car rental agency. Please type ‘motorcycle’ in the text area. For today, the following types of vehicles are still available on site:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks:",question:"Do you have a Porsche for rent today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have a Porsche on site today.",answer_template:"We have *.",type:"filler",target:"a Porsche",competitor:"a Ferrari",sameCategory1:"a fully overhauled Ford Mustang from 1968",sameCategory2:"a BMW convertible",otherCategory1:"a medium-sized delivery truck",otherCategory2:"a Volkswagen camper",correct_response:"motorcycle"},{itemName:"carRental-moving",settingName:"carRental",vignette_start:"You are working in a private car rental agency. Please type ‘motorcycle’ in the text area. For today, the following types of vehicles are still available on site:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks:",question:"Is a moving truck available on site?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have a moving truck on site today.",answer_template:"We have *.",type:"filler",target:"a moving truck",competitor:"a medium-sized delivery truck",sameCategory1:"a Dodge RAM pick-up truck",sameCategory2:"a Volkswagen camper",otherCategory1:"a BMW convertible",otherCategory2:"a Ferrari",correct_response:"motorcycle"},{itemName:"music-hardrock",settingName:"music",vignette_start:"You are driving in a car with your neighbor. Please type ‘classic’ in the text area. The car only has an old CD player. You have the following styles of music:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour neighbor asks:",question:"Do you have any hard rock?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have any hard rock.",answer_template:"I have some *.",type:"filler",target:"hard rock",competitor:"classic rock",sameCategory1:"heavy metal",sameCategory2:"power metal",otherCategory1:"cool jazz",otherCategory2:"bluegrass",correct_response:"classic"},{itemName:"music-softrock",settingName:"music",vignette_start:"You are driving in a car with your neighbor. Please type ‘classic’ in the text area. The car only has an old CD player. You have the following styles of music:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour neighbor asks:",question:"Do you have any soft rock?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have any soft rock.",answer_template:"I have some *.",type:"filler",target:"soft rock",competitor:"cool jazz",sameCategory1:"soul jazz",sameCategory2:"ambient",otherCategory1:"death metal",otherCategory2:"classic rock",correct_response:"classic"},{itemName:"airport-usa",settingName:"airport",vignette_start:"You are a customer service agent helping to book flights. Today there is ",vignette_continuation:"Please type ‘London’ in the text area.\\n\\nA customer asks:",question:"Do you have an afternoon flight to Boston?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have an afternoon flight to Boston today.",answer_template:"We have *.",type:"filler",target:"an afternoon flight to Boston",competitor:"a morning flight to Boston",sameCategory1:"an afternoon flight to San Francisco",sameCategory2:"an evening flight to Los Angeles",otherCategory1:"a flight to Australia",otherCategory2:"a flight to Europe",correct_response:"London"},{itemName:"airport-europe-UPDATED",settingName:"airport",vignette_start:"You are a customer service agent helping to book flights. Today there is",vignette_continuation:"Please type ‘London’ in the text area.\\n\\nA customer asks:",question:"Do you have a morning flight to Madrid?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have a morning flight to Madrid today.",answer_template:"We have *.",type:"filler",target:"a morning flight to Madrid",competitor:"a morning flight to Barcelona with connections to other airports",sameCategory1:"an afternoon flight to Madrid",sameCategory2:"an evening flight to Paris",otherCategory1:"a flight to New York",otherCategory2:"a flight to Toronto",correct_response:"London"}]},ddc9:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a("e622")},e622:function(e,t,a){}});
//# sourceMappingURL=app.9e9ea840.js.map